Dear ID Tech

My name is Brock Ellefson, I saw your listing for instructors for your summer programming camps and I am very interested in your programming instructor position. Mentoring children is something I enjoy and having the opportunity to help them understand and enjoy computing would change their lives and being a part of that would be incredible.

This is currently my third year studying Computer Science at Montana State University. Despite being an undergraduate, I have a lot of experience in programming. I am not the next Bill Gates nor Vint Cerf however I am very passionate about computer science, constantly pushing myself to expand my knowledge of coding. I programmed my first 2D game from scratch on Blitz Basic. It was complete with sprites as well as custom-made sounds. Right now I'm in the process of independently developing my first android app, GroupEffort, in my spare time. I possess a lot of patience when it comes to working with kids, not only was I a mentor for freshmen in high school, but I have also been a youth soccer coach for a brief time. Being a computer salesmen for Staples, I gained a lot of customer service experience selling software and answering any inquires a customers has.

An old boss of mine Samuel Quick, a network administrator, always thought merging my talented people skills with my knowledge of programming would be the best course for me. Hopefully you consider me a qualified applicant. Attached is my resume, feel free to contact me via cell phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.

Thank you for your time, Brock

brock**ellefson**

about

406-670-1796 brockellefson@live.com 1104 South Montana Ave. Bozeman, MT 59718

Currently studying Computer Science at Montana State University. Passionate about computer science, constantly pushing myself to expand my knowledge of coding. I take my work pridefully and put a great deal of effort in any current projects I am in.

areas of expertise

IDE:

Android Studio, Netbeans, Eclipse, Unity

Languages:

Java, C, ARMV8, Blitz Basic, Python, Perl

OS:

Windows, macOS, Android

education

Since 2014 Bachelors in Computer Science

work experience

2015-Now Cardinal Distribution - Lead Wine Loader

-OSHA certified to operate forklift

-Locate and load product on pallets for multiple routes

-Oversee wine department, make sure all pallets are picked

2014 - 2015 Staples EasyTec - Computer Salesman And Technician

-Sell Computers/Software

-Repair Computers

-Remote and in-store tech support

2013 - 2014 Red Lobster - Dishwasher, Baker

-Bake Bread

-Wash Dishes

-Clean kitchen, bathrooms

2013 - 2013 Dairy Queen - Grill Cook, Cashier

-Manage checkout

-Operate the drive-thru

misc.

2017 Association of Computing Machinery http://www.cs.montana.edu/ acm/

A student organization here at MSU dedicated to helping students who are going into the Computer Science Field. Meet regularly to plan new events, recruit new people, and reach out to local businesses for tours and advice.

2017 App and Game Development

Currently working on my first major app, GroupEffort. It will be used to help people find partners for homework and labs in their classes.

Also working on some 2d Unity-Based games for a few arcade machines I have

references

Samuel Quick (Mentor, Former Supervisor) +1(406)599-8145 Ryan Gallintine (Current Supervisor) +1(406)600-5185 Brandon Fouch (Former Supervisor) +1(406)539-1019